（稲妻の音）
（アランドロン）
＜むかしむかし　ある所に…てか→
Once upon a time, in a land far far away...
石矢魔高校という所に…
それは　それは凶悪で　残忍で→
Or rather, in a place called
"Ishiyama High School,"
there was a barbaric, ruthless, and defiant
bastard who thought nothing of his fellow man.
傍若無人で　人を人とも思わぬ
ヤツがおりました＞
（阿部）てめえが１年の男鹿か！？
オレは２年の阿部だ！！→
So you're the first year, Oga?
I'm Abe, a second year!
勝負しろ！！
Fight me!
（男鹿）フッ…。
≪オオーッ！２年の阿部と
１年坊の男鹿が勝負だ！≫
Second year Abe and the first
year punk Oga are gonna fight!
うるせえ…寝た子を
起こすんじゃね～よ　ハゲ。
Shut up. You're gonna wake the baby, baldy.
≪言っちまった！≫
≪やべ～ぞ！あの人　何て
呼ばれてるか知ってるか！？≫
Now he's said it!
Damn, does he know what this guy is called?
（阿部）へ～ッハハハ…！
≪キラーマシン　阿部！！≫
He's Abe the killing machine!
（不良達）オオ～ッ！
≪キラー！？怖え～！！≫
Killer?! Scary!
≪しかし　男鹿も硬中のデーモン・
アバレオーガと呼ばれた伝説の男！≫
But Oga is the legendary Rampaging
Demon Ogre of Kata Jr. High!
≪デーモン！？
かなり悪いな…≫
Demon? That's one seriously bad dude.
こいつは血の雨が降るぜ！
This guy rains blood!
のあ！見ろ　男鹿！
Hey, look at Oga!
≪あの男鹿が　ビビッてる？≫
Oga's turning chicken?
乗っとる…出とる…
乗って…出しとる。
He's on top... It's coming out...
He's on top and lettin' it go...
≪スゲ～　汗だ…男鹿も
キラーマシン阿部が相手じゃ…≫
Damn that's a lot of sweat.
I guess Oga isn't a match
for Abe the killing machine.
（水が流れる音）
違う　汗じゃねぇ！！
Wait, that's not sweat!
頭の上で！→
On his head!
赤ん坊が　おしっこしてる！
There's a baby pissing on his head!
（ざわめき）
（ベル坊）ダッ！
んな事は　ど～でもいい！
勝負だぁ～！
Whatever!
Fight me!
なに　人の頭の上で
ションベン漏らしてんだ　コラ！
Does my head look like a
urinal to you, you brat?
ギャ～　ハハハハ…。
（アランドロン）
＜これは　ひょんなことから
赤ん坊を育てることになった→
This is a story of a high school
juvenile delinquent who,
不良高校生の物語である。
ただし　その赤ん坊は→
through some strange circumstances,
is raising a baby.
But this baby is no ordinary baby.
普通の赤ん坊ではなく…＞
ダッ！…ダブ！
なんだ　その目は　コラ！
ダブダブダー！
What the hell is that look for?
なんだ　このガキャ～！
Who's the damn kid?
アウ！ン？…ン？
あっ？
アアア～…。
うわっ！
えっ？
ダッ！
うわ～っ！！
ビ～…。
ビエエエエエエ～ッ！！
（一同）ぎゃあ～！
（阿部）うわ…わわわ…。
I Picked up the Demon Lord
むかしむかし　あるところに
それはそれはハンサムで→
Once upon a time, in a land far away,
there was a handsome, cool, and popular
young man whom everyone looked up to.
格好良くてモテモテで
みんなから尊敬されまくっている→
心優しい若者がおりました。
Screw you, Oga!
（不良）((てめ…オガ…死ね))
Die!
心優しい若者は　こう言いました。
The kind hearted young man said this:
((全員　土下座！))
Everyone grovel before me!
（古市）待て待て！
Hold it, hold it...
Hmm?
むっ？
ダァ～！
「む？」じゃねぇ～よ
誰が心優しくてモテモテだ。
Don't "hmm" me!
Who's kind hearted and popular again?
ア～！
つか　その赤ん坊は
何なんだよ！あ！？
And what the hell is with the baby, huh?
バカめ　古市　それを
これから話そうとしてんだ…。
Silly little Furuichi, that's what
I was getting around to telling you.
話の腰を折るんじゃね～！！
（古市）あ～　痛い痛い痛い…。
Break my train of thought,
and I break your back!
ダァ～…。
続きを聞け！
Now listen up!
We apologize for rising
above our station just now.
((さっきは　調子こいて
すみませんでした。→
男鹿君が　あまりにも
無防備に寝てたもんだから→
You were just sleeping there so helplessly,
Oga-kun, that we thought it was our chance...
つい　チャンスと思って…))
((チャンスじゃね～よ　おまえ→
It wasn't a chance.
You know, if I were anybody
but me, I'd be dead.
あれ　オレじゃなかったら
死んでっぞ。ハハハハ…))
((いや～
本当にね…ハハハッ…→
Yeah, for real...
Sure wish you were dead...
死ねばよかったのに…ハハハ…))((ハハハッ…))
＜心優しい若者は…＞
The kind hearted young man...
((ゴボガベボゴ…))
＜川に洗濯に行きました＞
...went to do some washing up in the river.
（不良）((悪魔だ…ひでぇ))
＜すると…＞
He's a demon!
Dang...
And then...
Floating, floating...
（アランドロン）
((どんぶらこっこ　どんぶらこ
どんぶらこっこ…))
Floating, floating...
From upstream, a big guy came
floating, floating down the river...
＜川上の方から　大きなおっさんがどんぶらこっこと…＞
（古市）はい　スト～ップ…つ～か→
Okay, stop!
Where are you going with this story, and
what the hell do you mean, a "big guy?"
何？その話
どこへ持っていきたいの？
なんだよ
大きなおっさんって…。
流れてきたんだから
しかたあるまい。ダァ～イ！
He floated down the river! What can I say?
"Big guys" don't float down rivers, damn it!
（古市）
流れてこね～よ　そんなもん！
いや　たしかに
あれはオレも　超ビビったよ。
Well, it was definitely quite shocking.
実際　他のヤツらは
一目散に逃げてったからな。
Actually, all the other dudes turned
and ran the second they saw him.
ったりめ～だろ！！
Well, duh!
But the kind hearted young man
was not taken aback in fear,
＜だが　心優しい若者は
怯むことなく　たった一人で→
and all by himself, lifted
the big guy out of the river!
その大きなおっさんを
引き上げた＞
((オウ！))
Oh!
And then split him in half.
＜そして　２つに割ると…＞
((ブルッブルブル…あ…))
From inside, a spirited baby boy...
＜中から元気な男の子が…＞
割るな～っ！！
You split him?!
The young man said,
若者は言いました。
「おおっ　なんて可愛い赤ん坊」。
"Oh, what a cute baby!"
((アウ～？ア？…アウ～？))
《う～む…しかし　なんだこりゃ？まいったぞ　ど～する…》
But, what the hell?
Crap, what am I supposed to do?
((ダッ？　アウ～ウィ？))
((愛しい…))((あ？))
Precious...
Farewell!
（アランドロン）
((さよなら　私の…転送！))
((あ？))
Transfer!
((ダァ…))
((お？))
((ダ？アウ～…ウィ？))
((ん～…))
((ア～…))
The kind hearted young man stayed calm and
responded to the situation like an adult.
＜心優しい若者は　落ち着いて
大人の対応をしました＞
So kid...
((やあ　ボク　迷子？))
Are you lost?
((ア～ウ～　アウ～…))
《違うか？…
じゃあ　もっと爽やかに…》
Wait, I'm doing it wrong...
Maybe, more light hearted?
((よぉ～し　よしよし…！
違うか？→
There-there-there-there!
No, that's not...
ボウズ
蝋人形にしてやろうか！！))
Hey brat! I'll steal your very soul!
＜すると　赤ん坊は…＞
After that, the baby...
((ダッ！))
((うおっ！))
＜めっさ　なついた…＞
...got totally attached to me.
みたいな？
ダッ！
Or so it seems.
Enough already! Who the hell
would believe that story?
（古市）もういい！誰が
信じるんだよ　そんな話！→
いいから　早く元の所に
戻してこい！
Take him back to wherever
you got him from already!
ダァ！
You idiot!
あっ　バカ！
えっ？
まて　ガキ！これ見ろ→
Wait, kid!
Look at this!
ほら　カマドウマ！
カマドウマ！
See? It's a camel cricket!
何やってんだ　お前。
ア～。
バカ　さっき　これ効いたんだよ。
What the hell are you doing?
This totally worked before, idiot!
アウ！
あ…飽きてる！
Crap, he's bored with it.
いたたたた！
ビエエエエ～…。
（男鹿・古市）ぎゃああ～。
（爆発音）
（不良達）だ～っ！
バブ～…。
古市　お前
カマドウマ以下だな。
I guess you rank lower than
a camel cricket, Furuichi.
泣くと　こうなんだよ。だから
うかつに放り出せねぇ…。
This is what happens when he cries.
That's why you can't just
pull him away like that.
いや　それ　おかし～だろ！
し～っ！
Yeah, don't you think there's
something wrong with that?
アウ…。
バカ　古市！
Furuichi, you idiot!
でけぇ声を出すな！
Keep your voice down!
表に出ろ　こらぁ！
なんだとぉ　こらぁ～！
Let's take this out back, asshole!
Say what?
し～っ！！
You're going to make him cry again!
また泣きだしちまうだろ～が。
ビエ…！
うわっ！？
ビエエエエエ～…！
（一同）ぎゃあああ…！！
（爆発音）
（不良達）うわ～！
（ざわめき）
ダ～ブ！ダ～ブ！アウ～…！
とりあえず　今
オレたちに出来ることは→
Anyway, all we can do for
now is keep him distracted.
アウ！アウッ…！
こいつの機嫌をとる事だ。
"We" my ass!
ウ～…アウッ～！
「オレたち」じゃね～だろ！勝手に
オレまで巻き込んでんじゃねぇ！
Don't go mixing me up in this!
いいから　早く探せ！
Whatever, just hurry up and search!
バブ　バブ…。
こいつのハートをガッチリつかむ
ナンかをよ。
Find something that can
grab this brat's heart!
As if!
あるわけね～だろ…
ここは全国最凶ヤンキー率１２０％→
This is Ishiyama High, the worst school in the
entire country! We're 120% Grade A delinquents!
石矢魔高校なんだぜ…。
（不良達）
全国最凶～　ヤンキー率１２０％
石矢魔高校！
Ishiyama High! 120% JDs,
the worst in the country!
どうした　こらぁ！？
What's wrong?
男鹿が赤ん坊連れて来やがった。
Oga brought a baby with 'im!
あ…赤ちゃんだと！！
A baby?!
ダァ～…。
Idiot! Do something, Furuichi!
ビエ～…。
バカ　何とかしろ　古市！
考えろ　オレ！考えろ　オレ！
うう～…ハイ出た～！
Think, me! Think!
Bingo!
It's Count Poo, who appears
in the anime "Gohan-kun!"
（古市）アニメ「ごはん君」に
出て来る　うんこ男爵！
よし　見ろ！
Take a look!
アア…ブ！
うっ！
Furuichi!
古市！
ううっ…こうなったら仕方ない。
Then I've got no choice!
（古市）ピョ～ン！
ダブ？
ナイス　古市！
つ～か　何持ってんの　お前。
Nice, Furuichi!
And why do you have that with you?
コンビニでバイトしてる子に
プレゼントしようと思ってな。
I was thinking of giving it to the girl who
works at the convenience store as a present.
キモイな古市。
ンだと　コラッ！
Furuichi, you sicken me.
Screw you!
ダブ！
あっ！
ビエエエエ～！！
つ～か　あの赤ん坊はなんだ？
What the hell is that kid?
男鹿の子供か？
てか　人じゃね～だろ…。
Oga's kid?
Wait, that's no human.
何見てんだ　こらぁ！
ビエエエエ～！！
What the hell are you lookin' at?
（不良達）うわっ！
ぎゃあああ～！！
（爆発音）
ダブ～ブ～…。
My body can't take much more of this.
このままじゃ　身体がもたねぇ→
こうなったら残る方法は１つだ。
眠らせて　その隙に→
There's only one thing left to do.
Put him to sleep and stick him back
inside the big guy before he wakes up!
割れた大きな　おっさんの中に
戻してくるしかねぇ。
おっさん
まだ　割れたままなのかよ！！
The big guy's still split open?
てか　みぞ落ちに
一発とかはナシな。
I mean, I don't think we can just ditch 'im.
古市バカ！オレが
そんな非道な男に見えるか？
Furuichi, you idiot!
Do I look like such a cruel person?
（チャイム）
School Store
All sold out!
（お姉さん）売り切れ～！
（不良）じゃあ　アンパンは？
Then an anpan?
Sold out!
（不良）フルーツ牛乳は？
（お姉さん）売り切れ～！
Fruit milk?
Sold out.
じゃあ　カレーライスはぁ？
（お姉さん）は～い　売り切れ～！
Curry rice?
Yup, sold out.
じゃあ　何があるんじゃ　こらぁ！！
Then whaddya got left, damn it?
（不良達）おお～っ！！
（お姉さん）フッ…。
（不良達）う～…。
≪おりゃ～≫　≪こらぁ！≫
（殴る音）
（不良達）ハァ…ハァ…。
んがっ！
ちょっと　ゴメ～ン。
何するつもりだ？
Pardon me.
What are you planning on doing?
ダブ　ア～…。
バカめ　古市！
Furuichi, you're such an idiot.
腹一杯飯を食えば
眠くなるのが自然のキマリ。
It's only natural to get sleepy
after you fill up your belly!
待ってろ　今
腹一杯　食わせて…いねぇ！
（古市）あそこだ！
Just watch me! I'm gonna feed him plenty!
He's gone!
Over there!
焼そばパンは　ワシんじゃあ！
命かけてもいただくぜ！
The yakisoba bread is mine!
That bread is mine! I'll stake my life on it!
ダブ！
（不良達）あっ！？
ダッ！
ダブダ　ダブダ…ア～！
アウ！
（不良達）ああ～っ！
Yakisoba bread!
焼そばパ～ン！
俺んだぁ！
It's mine!
≪待て　こらぁ～！
どけこらぁ～！≫
Wait for me!
≪焼そばパ～ン！
待て　こらぁ！≫
Yakisoba bread, wait!
ダ…ダァ～ブ！
Hey, Oga...
なあ…男鹿　ひっとして
この赤ん坊　喜んでないか？
ギャア～…！！ダブ～！
Do you think the baby is... happy?
ア～…ダブ～！
アウ～ダブ　ダブ～！
What the hell is this baby?
この赤ん坊…
いったい何者なんだ？
ダブ～　ダブ～！
（アクババ）グエ～グエ～！
（アクババ）グァ～！！
It is time.
（ヒルダ）そろそろか…。
このあたりだ　くまなく探せ…。
He is near.
Leave no stone unturned.
フッ…。
Listen up, Furuichi...
聞け古市　ためになる話だ。
（古市）てか　何でウチに来た？
This might be to our benefit.
Wait, why are we at my house?
…むか～し　むかし
あるところに　それはそれは→
Once upon a time, there was
a fine young lumberjack.
いいキコリの若者が
いました。
Hold it!
待て！そのパターンは
もういい。
よ！
That joke is old now!
The young man threw his ax into lake, and
the spirit of the lake appeared and said,
若者が斧を泉に落とすと
泉の精が現れて→
"Was it this old ax you threw in the lake?
「お前の落としたのは
この古い斧か？それとも→
Or was it this golden baby?"
こっちの金の赤ん坊か？」と…。
Yeah, I saw that one a mile away.
やっぱ　そっちか…。
金の赤ん坊を　ど～ぞ！
イ～！
Here! Have a golden baby!
I ain't taking that thing!
オレは絶対　受け取らないからな！
そんな訳の分かんねえ赤ん坊。
Not some freaky baby!
I've got a date I'm going on tonight!
オレは　これからデートなんだよ！
なら　ちょうど
いいじゃねえか　彼女と２人。
Then, perfect!
You and that girl can raise him
and live happily ever after!
コイツを育てて幸せに暮らせ！
は　離れろコラ！
ダ！ヒ～。
Let go of me, you!
Listen up, baby!
おい赤ん坊！オレが本気で
怒ったら地獄を見るぞ！
ヒ～。
If you seriously make me mad...
I'll show you the pits of hell!
…ア～。
ダ～バ～！ア…。
古市。
（古市）おう…。
Furuichi.
Yeah.
めっさ　なついた。
He's totally attached to me.
Attached to you?
なついた？フン
勘違いも甚だしいな…。
You're delusional.
The Master would never
take to the likes of you!
貴様ごときに坊っちゃまが
なつく訳がなかろう。
Die, gutter-trash!
死ねドブ男。
うおおお…何？どなた？
W-Who might you be?
Who you callin' gutter-trash?
誰がドブ男だ　つ～か
そこ降りろ！
And get down from there, now!
Waltzing into my house like you own it!
人ん家でエラそうに
しやがって。
いや　オレん家。
Uh, it's my house.
Why are you pickin' a fight like always, Oga?
《何でフツーに
ケンカ売ってんだ男鹿。→
She ain't normal, dude!
こいつ何か変だろ！》
…フン。
Now, Master, come here.
さあ坊っちゃま　参りましょう。
ヒルダが→
Hilda is here to bring you home.
お迎えに上がりましたよ。迎えに？
Bring home?
ダ。
プ　いやがってますな～。
Looks like he doesn't like you!
Freaky...
やな顔。
えっと　坊っちゃま？
Come now, Master...
It is time to go!
ほら行きますよ。
ダ…ビ…。
Let go of him, Master!
お離し下さい　そんなもの…
坊っちゃま！
ビ～バ～。
はっは～参ったな　こりゃ～。
男鹿…何か分かんね～けど→
Oh, my! What am I to do?
Oga, maybe I'm missing something here...
But if you give the baby back to
her, won't that fix everything?
この人に赤ん坊返したら
問題解決じゃね？
She came to pick you up, you brat!
ほ～ら　お迎えだぞコラ～！
ブ～ダ～！
Furuichi, you idiot, help!
古市バカ　手伝え！
おう！おう！？
ビ　ビエエエ…。
（爆発音）
I apologize.
失礼しました。私　その赤子に
つかえる侍女悪魔→
I am the demon Hildegarde, and I
am this baby's maidservant demon.
ヒルデガルダと申します。
（男鹿・古市）《悪魔？》
Demon?
And that child is to be
the king of we demons.
そして　その方は我々魔族の王と
なられる　お方。
His name is...
名をカイゼル・デ・エンペラーナ・
ベルゼバブ４世。
Kaiser de Emperana Beelzebub IV.
In other words, he is the Demon Lord.
つまり　魔王でございます。
（大魔王）ウハハハ…。
Demon Lord?
魔王！？
You foolish humans, I will destroy you!
愚かな人間どもめ　滅ばしてやる！
魔王！
Demon Lord?
Demon Lord!?
（男鹿・古市）魔王！？
ダ～ブ～！
Son of mine, destroy humanity!
我が息子よ　人類を滅ぼすのだ！
ダブ～！
ブ。
えっと　ヒルダさん
でしたっけ？いいんですよ→
Um, Hilda-san, was it?
Thanks for the exposition!
That's great and all...
そ～ゆ～設定とかは　もう
オレ達　この子を→
But since you've come to take him
back, well, if you don't mind...
連れて帰ってさえくれたら
それで　もう…はい。
No, that won't be possible.
いえ　それは無理でございます。
何故なら　あなたは→
Why? Because you seem to have been chosen.
選ばれてしまったのですから…。
魔王の親に。
As the Demon Lord's father!
The Great Demon Lord said this:
大魔王様は　こう
おっしゃいました。
（大魔王）
((ハハハ…。あ　わし
明日から人間を滅ぼす。→
I'll get to destroying humanity tomorrow.
They're like, so annoying.
They breed like roaches.
なんかさ～あいつらさ～
ウザくない？→
増えすぎ！ってカンジでさ　全部
消し飛んだ方が→
Why don't we just, like,
totally wipe them out?
スカッとするよね～))
（側近）((ですが大魔王様　明日は→
But Great Demon Lord, tomorrow is
the Dark Dragon King's wedding.
冥竜王の結婚式が))
（大魔王）((マジで～？→
Really?
Then, the day after tomorrow.
じゃあ明後日！
明後日から絶対やる))
I'll definitely get to it
the day after tomorrow.
The day after is the hell-wide
chupacabra hunting bus tour.
((明後日からは　地獄チュパカブラ
大捜索バスツアーです))
Well, dang! I'm like, so super busy!
（大魔王）
((え～超多忙じゃん　わし))
And after that, the 10,000-day
mahjong marathon on Demon Isle.
((明明後日からは百日耐久
マージャン大会です))
Oh, forget it.
((あ～じゃあ　もういいや
あいつに　やらせよう。→
I'll have that kid I just had do it.
この前　生まれた　わしの息子。
ヒルダ))
((はい))
Hilda!
Yes?
Take him to the human world,
find some human to raise him,
（大魔王）((お前　あいつ人間界に
連れてってさ～　んで→
and have him destroy humanity, 'kay?
適当な人間に育てさせながら
滅ぼせ。な！))
...is what he said.
という訳でございまして。
大魔王…。
The Great Demon Lord...
Seems like he's got a screw loose.
（古市）適当だな…。
私どもは　坊っちゃまの親と
なるべき人間を探しに来たのです。
I have come here in search of a human
suitable to be the young Master's parent.
へ～。
ガンバ！
Good luck!
ちょ…お前
この状況で逃げんのかよ。
You just gonna run away?
This is my house! Go home!
てか　ここ
オレん家だし　帰れ！
Hell no!
だとコラ！
ダブ…。
I knew it! My eyes do not lie!
やはり私の目に狂いなし。
Who?!
誰？
次元転送悪魔のアランドロンだ。
This is the dimensional
transference demon, Alaindelon.
A dimensional transference
demon is just as the name says:
次元転送悪魔とは
その名の示す通り→
A demon that can transfer people
or things between the dimensions!
次元を超えて
人や物を転送する悪魔。ん～。
Transfer!
（アランドロン）((転送！いた！))
Ow!
（アランドロン）
私は魔界から坊っちゃまを
転送させる為→
In order to transfer the Master from the
Demon World, I floated down the river.
川に流されました。そして
薄れゆく意識の中。→
And, half conscious, I saw you standing and
laughing heartily as humans groveled before you!
あなたが大勢の人間を土下座させ
高笑いしているのを→
見たのです　確信いたしました。
ああ　この男になら→
I was convinced!
Ah! I can leave the Master
in this person's hands!
坊っちゃまを任せられると…。
So that's why!
あれが原因か～。
なるべくして　なったんだな。
It was your destiny.
You've got to be kidding me!
冗談じゃね～ぞ。何が魔王の親だ！ちょっとガキに→
The parent of the Demon Lord?
So the kid likes me a
little! Big effin' deal!
なつかれたくらいで
ふざけんなよ！オレは→
I ain't gonna to do it! No way!
ぜって～やらね～からな！
つまり　断ると？
In other words, you refuse?
Duh!
たりめ～だ！とっとと
持って帰れや！
…オイ。
Take him and leave, now!
Is that so?
そうですか　では死んで下さい。
Then, please die.
（男鹿・古市）あ…。
（爆発音）
Crap! She's actually a demon?
やべえ　まさか本当に
悪魔なのか？→
Wait, Oga!
待て男鹿！てめえ　あれ
絶対べんしょ～させるからな！→
You are so paying for repairs!
Yes you are, damn it!
絶対だかんな～！
うははは…。
What's this? This is a real laugh!
何だ　これ。何か笑えてきたぞ！
落ち着け古市！
Don't crack on me, Furuichi!
I can handle this!
オレは大丈夫だ。
いやダメだろ。背中に　まだ
ついてるぞ！
Hell no you can't!
He's still stuck on your back!
What? You damn...
何？このクソ…離れね～。
He won't come off!
Give up!
諦めろ！悪魔から
逃げられるとでも思ってるのか？
Did you think you could escape a demon?
うるせ～！一生そこで
カッコつけてろ！
Shut it!
Just stay up there forever
trying to look cool!
Akubaba!
アクババ！
キ～！キキキキ～。
Yup, she's a demon!
やっぱ悪魔だ！
男鹿キック！
Oga kick!
（アクババ）キ～。
蹴った！悪魔を蹴った。
You. Kicked. A. Demon!?
キャキャキャ…。
お前の　そ～ゆ～とこ尊敬するよ。
Okay, I kind of respect that about you!
It's important to hit 'em first!
先手必勝だ。
ハ！
（古市・男鹿）うわ～。
（爆発音）
Isn't that the Rampaging Ogre?
あれ　アバレ男鹿じゃね？
Looks like something's going down.
何か慌ててるみて～だな。
（男鹿・古市）あ　あ　あ…。
Hey, it's "Demon..." Runnin' from a woman?
おいおい　デーモンのやつ
あの女から逃げてんのか？
This is seriously our chance!
マジ？チャンス。
よし　あの女に加勢すっぞ！
Okay, we're gonna help that broad!
（古市・男鹿）はあ　はあ…。
You think you can escape?
それで逃げたつもりか？
魔王の親に→
You refuse, despite being
chosen by the Demon Lord.
選ばれたにもかかわらず
それを拒否…。
Demons are very picky
about contracts, you see.
悪魔は契約に　うるさくてな…。
死ね。
Die.
ダ…ウ～。
坊っちゃま？
Master?
Oga!
（不良達）男鹿！コラ～。
ギギ…ヤヤヤ…。
（不良達）へ？
ダ～～！
（爆発音）
（一同）わ…。
ビ…。
（一同）わ！
What is this? He's freakin' out?
何？かんしゃく？
これが悪魔の力。
Is this the power of a demon?
M-Master!
ぼ　坊っちゃま！だだを
こねないで下さいまし。
Please do not throw a tantrum!
Tantrum?! This is way beyond a tantrum!
ええ　だだ？だだってレベルじゃ
ないぞ　これ。は　男鹿は？→
Where's Oga?
He's unconscious!
気絶してる～っていうか
最悪　死んでる～。
Or worst-case dead?!
Can't you do something?
何とかならないんですか　これ。
このままじゃ→
This is seriously not going to end well!
マジで　やばいんじゃ。
無理です。
I cannot.
あ…。
ああなってしまっては→
When he gets like that, there
is no stopping the Master.
もう坊っちゃまを止める事は。
そんな　無理って。じゃあ→
You can't?
Then what are we supposed to do?
ど～すんですか　あれ！
だから　ど～しようも無いと
言っておろ～が！
I told you there's nothing to be done!
Only the Great Demon Lord could
calm a crying fit such as this...
こんな大泣き止められるのは
大魔王様くらいしか…。
（古市）あ…。
エイ…エ…。
A man shouldn't go crying like that.
男がギャアギャア泣くんじゃねえ。
ナメられちまうぞ。
People'll think you're weak.
He stopped!
《止まった…。そんなバカな
私にも止められなかった→
That's... impossible!
Even I couldn't stop him
when he cries like that...
大泣きを　たった
あれだけで》
And yet, with not so much as a...
ダ…ダ！
Good!
よ～し。じゃあ　もう泣くなよ。
Now, no more crying.
Bingo.
《決まった…》
ア～。
And don't follow me anymore.
もう　ついて来んじゃね～よ。
ダ…。
Master!
坊っちゃま～！
ウ！
What the hell am I doing?
《何やってんだ　オレ》
ワ～！
あ…。
鉄塔が消し飛んだ…。
He destroyed the steel tower!
I can't believe he resonated with the
Master and pulled out so much power!
坊っちゃまと感応し
これほどまでの力を引き出すとは。
何なのだ　この男は一体…。
（古市）男鹿～！
What the... Who in the world is he?
Oga!
あ！何かと思えば夢オチかよ。
Ah, man... A dream sequence?
That was the stupidest dream ever.
なんちゅ～アホな夢。しかし
あぶなかった～。あの流れだと→
Phew... With that setup, I was totally
gonna end up the parent of the Demon Lord!
確実にオレ　魔王の親じゃね～か。
フン　ようやく目覚めたか。
Finally awake, are we?
は？
丸２日も眠りこけおって
待ちくたびれたぞ。
It has been a full two days,
and I am tired of waiting.
Why are you here?
てめ　何で　ここに！つ～か
ずっと居たのか？
And wait, you were here the whole time?
What are you so surprised about?
何を驚いておる。あなたは魔王の親
今日から共に→
Starting from today, let us raise a
fine Demon Lord to destroy humanity.
人間を滅ぼす
立派な魔王を育てましょう。
ダ。ダ～ブ　ダ！
And there you have it.
The handsome, cool, popular,
and kind hearted young man
defeated the Demon Lord, and they
all lived happily ever after!
Yes, happily...
Hold it a second!
You didn't defeat him!
Nobody ended up happy!
And it's only the first episode!
Shut it, Furuichi!
I am not raising him, no way!
He's a baby Demon Lord, damn it!
On the next Beelzebub:
Say Hi to the BoB Brawler
Don't go doing previews on your own!